<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>alps on rudra kar</title>
    <link>https://rudra.dev/tags/alps/</link>
    <description>Recent content in alps on rudra kar</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://rudra.dev/tags/alps/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Northgate Omnikey Ultra</title>
      <link>https://rudra.dev/collections/northgate_omnikey_ultra/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 Apr 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rudra.dev/collections/northgate_omnikey_ultra/</guid>
      <description>History Northgate Computer Systems was founded in 1987, and they used to sell personal computers. They sold their products through direct marketing However, their Omnikey keyboards were sold through dealers. Before the introduction of Omnikey series keyboards, Northgate badged keyboards from several companies such as Focus and Monterey, and some of the initial Omnikey models are said to be manufactured by Focus.
The first generation of Omnikey models was sold in the late ’88s, and the Omnikey Ultra series was manufactured in the mid-’90s.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Monterey K104</title>
      <link>https://rudra.dev/collections/monterey_k104_alps_skcm/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 17 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rudra.dev/collections/monterey_k104_alps_skcm/</guid>
      <description>History This keyboard was manufactured by Monterey  in the &amp;rsquo;90s. This model came with varieties of switches, including the Alps SKCM white and blue, SMK alps mounts, and &amp;ldquo;alps.tw Type OA2&amp;rdquo;. This particular board has Alps SKCM whites. This board is a Plantron branded keyboard, and the sticker on the back says that Plantron manufactured it. I couldn&amp;rsquo;t find more details about this particular company. As per another back sticker, this board was manufactured in April 1992.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Apple Extended Keyboard II</title>
      <link>https://rudra.dev/collections/apple_extended_keyboard_ii/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 15 Mar 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://rudra.dev/collections/apple_extended_keyboard_ii/</guid>
      <description>History Apple manufactured this board in the late &amp;rsquo;80s and early 90s. This board was the successor of the venerable Apple Extended Keyboard. These boards were included with Apple professional desktops starting with the Macintosh IIsi  .
These boards use either Alps or Mitsumi switches. The Mitsumi switches were only used on boards made in Japan. M3501s are said to be the last &amp;ldquo;Mechanical Keyboards&amp;rdquo; that apple has ever made.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
